Definitely not past sleeping together.
Warning signs were there.
(Penny:)This is really on you.
My God, I though you were my friend!
l don't think that was helpful.
(Howard:)Hi, Bernie, it's me again.
Please call me back.
Dude, I'm so sorry.
It's not your fauIt, it's mine.
l did all that stuff, not you.
(Leonard:)Actually, you did do
one of them together.
(Sheldon:)- Here.
- What is this?
(Sheldon:)You're upset. The convention is to bring
an upset person a hot beverage.
(Howard:)No, but what is it?
(Sheldon:)Chicken broth.
It seemed cuIturally appropriate.
(Sheldon:)There was a single cube of chicken bouillon
in the cupboard when I moved in.
(Sheldon:)And it's been bothering me
for the last eight years.
(Sheldon:)So as they say, two birds.